Guide to the New York University Portrait Files MC.319
New York University Archives
New York University Archives Portrait Files
1857-2006
circa 1960s-1990s
New York University Archives
New York University. Photo Bureau
MC.319
53.69 Linear Feet in 121 manuscript boxes, two half manuscript boxes, and a flat box
16.3 Megabytes in 7 computer files
The New York University Archives Portrait Files (dated 1857-2006) is an artificial collection created by the University Archives as a central collection for photographs and portraits of individuals associated with the University. The collection consists of photographs, negatives, slides, and contact sheets depicting New York University administrators, faculty, staff, alumni, donors, trustees, and invited guests.
Arrangement
This collection is arranged in a single file listing in alphabetical order by last name.
Conditions Governing Access
Materials are open without restrictions.
Scope and Contents
The New York University Archives Portrait Files (dated 1857-2006) is an artificial collection created to centralize information on individuals associated with the University. The collection consists of photographs, negatives, slides, and contact sheets depicting New York University administrators including NYU Presidents L. Jay Oliva, James McNaughton Hester, and John Brademas; faculty and staff including Professors Bayrd Still and Sylvia Law; alumni and donors including Martin Scorsese, Neil Diamond, and Spike Lee; trustees including Julius Silver and Jillian Manus-Salzman; and invited guests including Eleanor Roosevelt, Danny Kaye, and Jackie Robinson. The types of photographs found in this collection include professional headshots, promotional photographs, candid photographs, photographs from events, and some family photographs.
Within the inventory, there are instances of names repeating. These are different individuals with the exact same name.
Historical Note
The New York University Archives Portrait Files was created by the University Archives to make a central collection for reference staff fulfilling requests for information on individuals associated with the University.
Custodial History
No information was recorded about the acquisition of the materials in this collection. There are two accessions related to this collection: 2021.008 and 2022.037.
Appraisal
During the course of reprocessing in 2025, the Processing Archivist identified collection material that does not belong in the collection due to format or scope. Memorandum, articles, resumes, correspondence, and other types of paper materials containing biographical information was moved to the New York University Archives Biographical Files (MC 317).
Photographs of student activities, busts from the University Heights campus' Hall of Fame for Great Americans, and the Washington Square Festival were removed and placed into the New York University Archives Photograph Collection (PHOTO 00001). Photographs of artwork by Andy Warhol, Hale Woodruff, and Edward Hopper were also removed and placed into PHOTO 00001. Non-portrait photographs related to John W. Draper and Henry Draper were moved also moved to PHOTO 00001. Non-portrait photographs related to Samuel F.B. Morse were removed and added to the Samuel F.B. Morse Papers (MC 10).
Materials related to Frank Gould and Emma B. Kennedy (Mrs. John Stuart Kennedy) were removed and placed into the collection file for MC 319.
Materials related to Joseph Smalley were removed and placed into the Matthew Wise Collection on the Joseph Smalley AIDS Memorial Quilt Panel (MC 422).
Negatives were reviewed by the Processing Archivist to determine whether they should remain in the collection or be removed. Negatives with printed photograph versions were discarded, while negatives without print photograph versions were considered unique and kept in the collection.
During reprocessing, several optical discs and a zip disk containing photographs were identified. Materials clearly labeled Photo Bureau were deaccessioned from the collection. Similarly, if physical print copies of digital photographs existed in the collection, the digital photographs were deaccessioned from the collection.
Born-Digital Access Policies and Procedures
An access terminal for born-digital materials in the collection is available by appointment for reading room viewing only. Researchers may view an item's original container and/or carrier, but the physical carriers themselves are not available for use because of preservation concerns.
Negatives (photographic); Slides (photographs); Contact sheets.; Black-and-white photographs.; Color photographs.; Portrait photography.; Brademas, John, 1927-2016; Oliva, L. Jay (Lawrence Jay), 1933-2014; Still, Bayrd; Law, Sylvia A.; Scorsese, Martin; Diamond, Neil; Lee, Spike; Silver, Julius; Manus-Salzman, Jillian; Roosevelt, Eleanor, 1884-1962; Kaye, Danny; Robinson, Jackie; Hester, James M., 1924-2014
- A
  - Aaron, Bennett L., undated (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Aaronson, Doris, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Abbe, Richard, 1964-1965 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Abbott, Austin, undated (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Abbott, George, undated (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Abbott, James, undated (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Abbott, Lyman and Daughter, circa 1912 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Abder, undated (Box 118, Folder 1)
  - Abee, William, circa 1934 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Abel, Daniel, 1983-1984 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Abeles, Joseph C., undated (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Abelson, Raziel, undated (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Abernathy, Mike, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Abernethy, Jane, undated (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Abis, Sidney, circa 1939 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Abi-Saab, Georges, undated (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Abraham, William I., 1961 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Abrahamson, Arnold, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Abrams, George J., 1962 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Abrams, Joan, undated (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Abrams, Richard, undated (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Abrams, Robert, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 21, Box 123, Folder 1)
  - Abramson, Stephanie, undated (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Abu-Lughad, Lila, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Abzug, Bella, circa 1970s-1990s (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Achenback, Gertrude, undated (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Acheson-Wallace, Lila, undated (Box 118, Folder 2)
  - Ackerman, Bernard A., 1976 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Ackerman, George, undated (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Ackerman, James, undated (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Ackerman, Mona, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Acosla, Marie, undated (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Acton, Sir Harold, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 31, Box 123, Folder 2)
  - Adam, Thomas R., 1961 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Adamiak, Theodore J., circa 1940s (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Adams, E. Sherman, undated (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Adams, Harriet Dyer, 1945 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Adams, Harvey, 1965 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Adams, Dr. Herbert W., 1940 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Adams, James Truslow, 1937 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Adams, John V., undated (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Adams, Mark H., 1942 (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Adams, Stanley, undated (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Adams, Warren S., 1903 (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Addams, Jane, 1965 (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - Addelston, Harold K., 1956 (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - Addoms, Elizabeth C., 1957 (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - Adelson, Jerry J., undated (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - Adesnik, Milton, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 47)
  - Adkins, Nelson F., undated (Box 1, Folder 48)
  - Adler, Blum, undated (Box 118, Folder 3)
  - Adler, Charles Jr., 1952 (Box 1, Folder 49)
  - Adler, Henry, undated (Box 1, Folder 50)
  - Adler, Julius Ochs, 1955 (Box 1, Folder 51)
  - Adler, Stella, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 52)
  - Aferton, Franklin C. III., 1980 (Box 1, Folder 53)
  - Affron, Charles, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 54)
  - Agnew, Hugh E., 1942 (Box 1, Folder 55)
  - Agnew, Peter L., 1964, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 56)
  - Aguilar, Rafael Angel, undated (Box 1, Folder 57)
  - Ahearn, Cornelius, undated (Box 1, Folder 58)
  - Ahrens, Edward H., 1984 (Box 1, Folder 59)
  - Ahrens, Ronald A., undated (Box 1, Folder 60)
  - Aigner, Lucien, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 61)
  - Akbelen, Ayda, undated (Box 1, Folder 62)
  - Akerele, Dr. Adebayo, undated (Box 1, Folder 63)
  - Akers, John F., 1987 (Box 1, Folder 64)
  - Akzin, Benjamin, 1955 (Box 1, Folder 65)
  - Al, El-Mohammed, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 66)
  - Albee, Edward, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 67)
  - Alberding, Russell J., undated (Box 1, Folder 68)
  - Albert, David, 1983-1984 (Box 1, Folder 69)
  - Albert, Marv, undated (Box 1, Folder 70)
  - Albornez-Sanchez, Nicholas, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 71)
  - Alcott, John, undated (Box 1, Folder 72)
  - Alden, Carlos C., undated (Box 1, Folder 73)
  - Alderblum, Evelyn, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 74)
  - Alejandro, José, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 75)
  - Alexander, Andrea, undated (Box 1, Folder 76)
  - Alexander, Bruce, 1964 (Box 1, Folder 77)
  - Alexander, Charles III, undated (Box 1, Folder 78)
  - Alexander, Fritz, 1982-1984, 1988, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Alexander, George, 1959 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Alexander, Lamar, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Alexander, Margaret, undated (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Alexander, Robert, undated (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Alfano, Michael C., undated (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Alfonsin, Raul, 1985-1986 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Alfonso, 1948 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Alford, Leon Pratt, 1937 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Allen, B.S., 1918 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Allen, Benjamin C., 1964-1965 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Allen, Catherine L., 1957 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Allen, Dave, undated (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Allen, Florence E., 1960 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Allen, Gay Wilson, 1955 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Allen, Jerome, undated (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Allen, John Stuart, undated (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Allen, R.E., 1988 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Allen, Robert E., undated (Box 118, Folder 4)
  - Allen, William, undated (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Allen, Woody, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Allenby, Field Marshal Edmund Henry Hyman, undated (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Allenby, John Edward, undated (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Alpenfels, Ethel J., 1960, 1965, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Alpert, Carol, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Alpert, Judith, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Alter, Mark, undated (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Altman, Edward, 1974, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Altman, Lawrence K., 1979 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Altman, Sidney, circa 1942 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Altshuler, Alan, 1983, 1986-1987 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Alverso, Vincent, 1960 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Amanpour, Christiane, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Amato, Giuliano, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - Amberg, George H., 1970 (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Amelar, Richard D., circa 1984-1985 (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - Amen, John H., 1953 (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - Amenta, Edwin, undated (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - Ames, Amyas, undated (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - Ames, Peter, undated (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - Amgott, Margo, undated (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - Amichai, Yehudi, 1981-1984 (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - Amon, Jerry, 1959 (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - Amoroso, Denise, undated (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - Amot, David, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - Amram, David, undated (Box 2, Folder 45)
  - Amsterdam, Birdie, undated (Box 2, Folder 46)
  - Amsterdam, Tony, 1983-1984 (Box 2, Folder 47)
  - Andersen, Susan, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 48)
  - Anderson, Carl, undated (Box 2, Folder 49)
  - Anderson, Celia, 1960 (Box 2, Folder 50)
  - Anderson, Claude, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 51)
  - Anderson, Helene, 1993-1994 (Box 2, Folder 52)
  - Anderson, John, undated (Box 2, Folder 53)
  - Anderson, Larry, 1960, 1964 (Box 2, Folder 54)
  - Anderson, Nancy G., undated (Box 2, Folder 55)
  - Anderson, Rodney, 1965 (Box 2, Folder 56)
  - Anderson, Thomas J., 1942 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Anderson, W.G., undated (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Anderson, Walter, 1953, 1959, 1963-1964 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Anderson, Warren, undated (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Anderson-Tirre, Loredana, 1999 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Andreatta, Beniamo, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Andreotti, Giulio, 1989 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Andrews, John N., 1940 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Andrews, Max, 1957 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Andrews, Richards, undated (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Andrews, Ruth, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Angell, Frank J., 1984 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Angelou, Maya, undated (Box 118, Folder 5)
  - Angoff, Allen, undated (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Annan, Noël Gilroy, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Annenberg, Walter H., undated (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Anthon, George C., undated (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Anton, Hector, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Antonoff, Stanley, undated (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Aoki, Chaye, undated (Box 118, Folder 6)
  - Apfel, Iris and Carl, 2002 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Apfelberg, Benjamin, undated (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Appelfeld, Aharon, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Appel, Jack I., 1985 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Appel, Morris Lionel, undated (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Appleton, Herbert M. Jr., undated (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Apostol, Paul, 1966 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Aquino, Corazon, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Aranya, Nissim, undated (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Archer, undated (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Arden, Kevin J., undated (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - Ares, Charles E., 1965 (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - Argelander, Ron, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - Arhweiler, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - Ariav, Gadi, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - Arkin, Alvin M., undated (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - Arlen, Harold, undated (Box 118, Folder 7)
  - Arlo, Raymond, 1965 (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - Arm, Adolph, undated (Box 3, Folder 36)
  - Armentrout, Lynn, 1989 (Box 3, Folder 37)
  - Armsay, James W., 1975 (Box 3, Folder 38)
  - Armstrong, Estelle, 1964 (Box 3, Folder 39)
  - Armstrong, G., undated (Box 3, Folder 40)
  - Armstrong, George E., 1955, 1966-1967 (Box 3, Folder 41)
  - Armstrong, John, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 42)
  - Armstrong, John C., 1967, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 43)
  - Armstrong, William (Bill), 1977 (Box 3, Folder 44)
  - Arndt, Christian O., 1957, 1961, 1963 (Box 3, Folder 45)
  - Arnoff, Frances, undated (Box 3, Folder 46)
  - Arnold, Arthur Z., undated (Box 3, Folder 47)
  - Arnold, Dorothy McSparren, undated (Box 118, Folder 8)
  - Arnold, James Loring, undated (Box 3, Folder 48)
  - Arnold, Joan C., undated (Box 3, Folder 49)
  - Arnold, Lea, 2000 (Box 3, Folder 50)
  - Arnold, Lea S., 1998 (Box 3, Folder 51)
  - Arnold, Lee, 1958, 1961, 1964 (Box 3, Folder 52)
  - Arnold, Vladimir, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 53)
  - Arnold-Foster, U., undated (Box 3, Folder 54)
  - Arnot, David E., 1987 (Box 3, Folder 55)
  - Aronovitz, Thomas, circa 1933 (Box 3, Folder 56)
  - Aronow, undated (Box 3, Folder 57)
  - Aronson, Dr. Allan R., undated (Box 3, Folder 58)
  - Aronson, James, undated (Box 3, Folder 59)
  - Arrowsmith, William, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 60)
  - Arthur, James, undated (Box 3, Folder 61)
  - Arthur, Sally, 1984, 1989 (Box 3, Folder 62)
  - Arvay, Diane (Miss NYU), 1960-1961 (Box 3, Folder 63)
  - Asarch, Joel K., undated (Box 3, Folder 64)
  - Asgis, Alfred J., undated (Box 3, Folder 66)
  - Ashe, Arthur, 1984 (Box 3, Folder 65)
  - Ashley, Clarence D., 1928 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Ashley, Joyce, 1994-1995 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Ashton, Earl S., undated (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Asimov, Isaac, 1983 (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - Asimov, Stanley, undated (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Askew, Reuben, undated (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Asner, Ed, 1984 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Assael, Henry, 1974 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Assael, Shaun, 1983 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Aster, Alvin K., 1953 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Astor, Brooke, 1965, 1972, 1992 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Atkins, Willard Earl, 1942 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Atkinson, Miles, 1944 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Atkinson, Philip S., 1961 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Atkinson, William H., undated (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Atting, I., undated (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Atyeo, Henry C., 1959 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Auchinclass, Louis, 1983 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Auerbach, Morris, 1956 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Auletto, Len, 1960-1963 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Aumuller, Albert C., 1942 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Austin, Theresa, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Austria, Agnes, 1986 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Ausubel, Carol R., undated (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Auer, Harold, undated (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Axelrod, Felicia, undated (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Axelrod, Julius, 1998
    - Photographs (Box 4, Folder 26)
    - Negatives (Box 118, Folder 9)
  - Axelrod, M.S., undated (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - Axtelle, George E., undated (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - Ayala, Francisco, 1964, 1986 (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - Ayers, Leen, 1967 (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - Ayearst, Morley, 1958 (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - Aymar, Francis W., undated (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - Azmita, Efrain, 1992
    - Photographs (Box 4, Folder 34)
    - Negatives (Box 118, Folder 10)
- B
  - Baar, Stanley, undated (Box 4, Folder 35)
  - Babcock, E.B., 1925 (Box 4, Folder 36)
  - Babian, Haig, undated (Box 4, Folder 37)
  - Baccus, Stephen, 1981 (Box 4, Folder 38)
  - Backer, Finn, undated (Box 4, Folder 39)
  - Backman, Jules, 1970-1976 (Box 4, Folder 40)
  - Backstrand, Jeffrey, 1995 (Box 4, Folder 41)
  - Badger, Philip O., undated (Box 4, Folder 42)
  - Badillo, Herman, 1970 (Box 4, Folder 43)
  - Baer, Dan, 1984 (Box 4, Folder 44)
  - Baer, Norbert S., undated (Box 4, Folder 45)
  - Baer, William B., 1927-1955 (Box 4, Folder 46)
  - Baghassarian, Jack, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 47)
  - Bagnoni, Laura, undated (Box 118, Folder 11)
  - Bailey, Glenn W., undated (Box 4, Folder 48)
  - Bailey, Herbert L., undated (Box 4, Folder 49)
  - Bain, Beverly, 1996 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Baird, Henry Martyn, 1887, 1889, 1902 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Baird, W.C., 1906 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Baker, Cornelius, 1926 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Baker, Curtis, undated (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Baker, Dr., 1972 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Baker, Elmer E., 1961, 1972, 1987 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Baker, G. Derwood, 1962 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Baker, John, 1996, 1999 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Baker, Keora, undated (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Baker, Russell, 1963 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Baker, Tracey, undated (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Bakst, Aaron, undated (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Balakian, Anna, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Balasubramanian, Arun, undated (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Baldwin, Alec, 1994-1995 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Baldwin, Janet, undated (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Baldwin, Judy, circa 1970-1971 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Baldwin, Marshall W., 1970 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Baldwin, William, undated (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Ball, Edith L., 1962 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Ball, Laurence, 1987 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Balliet, Thomas M., 1914 (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Balokian, Anna, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Balter, Dr. Lawrence, 1976, 1979-1980 (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - Baltzly, Alexander, undated (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - Bamberger, Paul, 1983 (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - Bander, Edward J., 1966 (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - Bandler, Jean, undated (Box 118, Folder 12)
  - Banks, Hugh C., 1969, 1971, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - Bantas, Hugh, undated (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - Bar-Gill, Oren, undated (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - Barak, Ahron, 1983 (Box 5, Folder 32)
  - Barasch, Dr. Frances K., 1979 (Box 5, Folder 33)
  - Barash, Phyllis, undated (Box 5, Folder 34)
  - Barber, Robert, undated (Box 5, Folder 35)
  - Barber, Victor, undated (Box 5, Folder 36)
  - Barberi, Andrew, 1964 (Box 5, Folder 37)
  - Barbie, Bonnie, 1979 (Box 5, Folder 38)
  - Barden, Al, 1960 (Box 5, Folder 39)
  - Bardes, Philip, undated (Box 5, Folder 40)
  - Baring, George Rowland Stanley (Earl of Cromer), 1966 (Box 5, Folder 41)
  - Barish, Norman, 1955, 1964 (Box 5, Folder 42)
  - Barkas, Loula, 1984 (Box 5, Folder 43)
  - Barkin, Leonard, 1990, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 44)
  - Barkow, Rachel, undated (Box 5, Folder 45)
  - Barlis, Tom, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 46)
  - Barmak, Jack, undated (Box 5, Folder 47)
  - Barnard, Darrell, undated (Box 5, Folder 48)
  - Barnes, Carl, 1953 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Barnes, Charles Randall, 1906 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Barnes, Clive, 1970 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Barnes, Cyrus W., 1953 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Barnett, Meg, undated (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Barnett, Scott F., undated (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Barney, Denise, 1976 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Baron, Louis, undated (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Baronski, Frances, 1974 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Baroudi, Jack, 1983 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Barr, Edward E., 1962 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Barr, Jean, 1981 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Barr, Sherman, 1982 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Barr, Stuart, undated (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Barre, Raymond, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Barres, Herster "Hertie", undated (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Barret, Hope, 1993 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Barrett, William C., 1959, 1978 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Barrie, George, 1988 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Barroncini, John, 1959 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Barrows, David N., undated (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - Barrymore, Ethel, 1952 (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - Barsotti, Claudia, undated (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - Bartels, Theodore R., 1967 (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - Bartiromo, Maria, 1999 (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - Bartley, Robert L., undated (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - Bartlett, Craig S., undated (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - Bartolomei, Jeanne, 1961 (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - Barton, Betsey, 1948 (Box 6, Folder 29)
  - Barton, Clara, undated (Box 6, Folder 30)
  - Barton, Harold, undated (Box 6, Folder 31)
  - Barton, Nancy, undated (Box 6, Folder 32)
  - Bartow, Arthur, undated (Box 6, Folder 33)
  - Baruch, Sylvia, 1981 (Box 6, Folder 34)
  - Basil, Teddy, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 35)
  - Baskin, Samuel, undated (Box 6, Folder 36)
  - Baslaw, Annette, 1984 (Box 6, Folder 37)
  - Bassine, Charles C., 1965 (Box 6, Folder 38)
  - Bassiri, Irsa, undated (Box 6, Folder 39)
  - Bassman, Jack, undated (Box 6, Folder 40)
  - Bassowitz, Harold, undated (Box 6, Folder 41)
  - Bates, A. Allan, 1961 (Box 6, Folder 42)
  - Bates, Joe, 1970 (Box 6, Folder 43)
  - Bates, Kathy, 1983 (Box 6, Folder 44)
  - Bates, Len, undated (Box 118, Folder 13)
  - Baudin, Maurice, undated (Box 6, Folder 45)
  - Bauer, Marion E., undated (Box 6, Folder 46)
  - Baughman, George, 1958 (Box 6, Folder 47)
  - Baukson, undated (Box 6, Folder 48)
  - Baum, Werner A., 1965 (Box 6, Folder 49)
  - Baumberger, Roger K., undated (Box 6, Folder 50)
  - Baumol, William, 1979, 1982, 1987-1989, 1992
    - Photographs (Box 6, Folder 51)
    - Negatives (Box 118, Folder 14)
  - Bay, Willow, undated (Box 6, Folder 52)
  - Baylor, Don, 1983 (Box 6, Folder 53)
  - Bayly, Winder R., 1973, 1981 (Box 6, Folder 54)
  - Baynes, undated (Box 6, Folder 55)
  - Baxter, Graeme, undated (Box 6, Folder 56)
  - Beaman, Florence N., undated (Box 6, Folder 57)
  - Beame, Abraham, 1975 (Box 6, Folder 58)
  - Bean, Carolyn, undated (Box 6, Folder 59)
  - Beanstock, undated (Box 6, Folder 60)
  - Beard, Anne, undated (Box 118, Folder 15)
  - Bearden, Romare, undated
    - Photographs (Box 6, Folder 61)
    - Negatives (Box 118, Folder 16)
  - The Beatles, 1964 (Box 6, Folder 62)
  - Beatty, Francis, circa 1936 (Box 6, Folder 63)
  - Beauchamp, Mary, 1954 (Box 6, Folder 64)
  - Beaumont, André, 1965 (Box 6, Folder 65)
  - Beaumont, Enid, 1976 (Box 6, Folder 66)
  - Beck, Martin L., 1961 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Becker, Abe, undated (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Becker, James, undated (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Becker, LaFollete, undated (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Becker, Murray, 1953, 1969 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Becker, Richard, 1971 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Becker, Ruth, undated (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Becker, Stuart, undated (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Beckett, Samuel, 1986 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Bederson, Benjamin, 1978-1979
    - Photographs (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - Negatives (Box 118, Folder 18)
  - Bedford, Gunning S., undated (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Bedrosian, Hrach, 1984
    - Photographs (Box 7, Folder 12)
    - Negatives (Box 118, Folder 19)
  - Beebe, Diane, undated (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Beekman, Fenwick, undated (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Been, Vicki, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Beers, William, 1978-1981 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Began, Martin, 1975 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Begelman, Jack, undated (Box 7, Folder 18)